Contact

cccjenculb@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jenculbertson-27405221 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Advocacy
Leadership

Jen Culbertson

CNO at Providence Health & Services

Medford, Oregon Area

Summary

My life journey has led me to healthcare. I am the mother of three adult children. Two of my kids have dealt with illness and life long health issues. I am able to bring my past experiences and incorporate them into my current practice as an RN, patient advocate, and voice of the staff. I believe in compassion and respect.

Experience

Providence Health & Services CNO October 2019 - Present (10 months) Medford, Oregon Area

Mercy Hospitals of Bakersfield Chief Nursing Officer April 2016 - October 2019 (3 years 7 months)

Mercy Hospitals Bakersfield, Southwest Senior Director of Patient Care Services November 2014 - April 2016 (1 year 6 months)

Education

CSU Bakersfield MSN · (2007 - 2009)